{"data":[{"id":0,"question":"Who is the 999th Lord Commander of the order of The Nights' Watch?","options":["Jon Snow","Alliser Thorne","Eddison Tollett ","Jeor Mormont"],"correct":"Eddison Tollett ,"},{"id":1,"question":"This sigil belong to which house?","options":["Dondarrion","Poole","Cerwyn","Tarth"],"correct":"Tarth,"},{"id":2,"question":"Who said “There's no cure for being a c*nt?”","options":["Jaime Lannister","Cersei Lannister","Tyrion Lannister","Bronn"],"correct":"Bronn,"},{"id":3,"question":"What are House Bolton's words?","options":["Here we stand","Righteous in wrath","Proud and free","Our blades are sharp"],"correct":"Our blades are sharp,"},{"id":4,"question":"Where is the seat of house Manderly?","options":["White Harbor","Barrowtown","Moat Cailin","Last Hearth"],"correct":"White Harbor,"},{"id":5,"question":"Who did Daenerys's dragon kill at Astapor?","options":["Xaro Xhoan Daxos","Pyat Pree","Kraznys mo Nakloz","Mirri Maz Duur"],"correct":"Kraznys mo Nakloz,"},{"id":6,"question":"Which giant was killed in the tunnel under the wall during the Wildlings' attack (on the wall)?","options":["Wun Weg Wun Dar Wun","Fug Men Fug Tun Ben","Mag Mar Tun Doh Weg","Dongo"],"correct":"Mag Mar Tun Doh Weg,"},{"id":7,"question":"Which city was Lady Crane's company traveling to after meeting Arya at Braavos?","options":["Pentos","Volantis","Lorath","Myr"],"correct":"Pentos,"},{"id":8,"question":"Which dragon's skull was Qyburn's scorpion tested on by Queen Cersei?","options":["Meraxes","Vermithrax","Vhagar","Balerion the Dread"],"correct":"Balerion the Dread,"},{"id":9,"question":"Who said \"Power resides where men believe it resides. It's a trick; a shadow on the wall\"?","options":["Petyr Baelish","Varys","Davos Seaworth","Tyrion Lannister"],"correct":"Varys,"},{"id":10,"question":"What is the Dothraki's sacred city called?","options":["Vaes Dothrak","Vaes Diaf","Vaes Leqse","Vaes Khewo"],"correct":"Vaes Dothrak,"},{"id":11,"question":"What city or town is nearest to Castle Black down south?","options":["Queenscrown","Last Hearth","Karhold","Mole's Town"],"correct":"Mole's Town,"},{"id":12,"question":"When Princess Shireen told Ser Davos this story; \"He polished his shield for a week so that it was like a mirror. And he crouched behind it and crept forward, hoping the dragon would only see its own reflection.\" Who was she referring to?","options":["Prince Daeron Targaryen","Ser Heather Alexander","Ser Byron Swann","Ser Duncan the Tall"],"correct":"Ser Byron Swann,"},{"id":13,"question":"What is the Northern most sea in the known world?","options":["The Jade Sea","The Narrow Sea","The Shivering Sea","The Summer Sea"],"correct":"The Shivering Sea,"},{"id":14,"question":"Who convinced Ned Stark to spare the lives of the direwolves' pups and give one to each of his children?","options":["Robb Stark","Theon Greyjoy","Jory Cassel","Jon Snow"],"correct":"Jon Snow,"},{"id":15,"question":"Which character said; \"Any man who must say 'I am the King' is no true King\"?","options":["Tywin Lannister","Bronn","Tyrion Lannister","Sandor \"The Hound\" Clegane"],"correct":"Tywin Lannister,"},{"id":16,"question":"Who is the Blackfish?","options":["Edmure Tully","Brann Tully","Hoyster Tully","Brynden Tully"],"correct":"Brynden Tully,"},{"id":17,"question":"What house does the Three-Eyed Raven belong to?","options":["Karstark","Greyjoy","Targaryen","Baratheon"],"correct":"Targaryen,"},{"id":18,"question":"Who is this?","options":["Harald Karstark","Greatjon Umber","Smalljon Umber","Ned Umber"],"correct":"Smalljon Umber,"},{"id":19,"question":"How are Lyanna Mormont and Jorah Mormont related?","options":["They are not related","Father and daughter","Cousins","Uncle and niece"],"correct":"Cousins,"},{"id":20,"question":"Who was always first to battle?","options":["Ned Stark","Randyll Tarly","Robert Baratheon","Tywin Lannister"],"correct":"Randyll Tarly,"},{"id":21,"question":"Who is the \"Late lord .....\"?","options":["Mace Tyrell","Yohn Royce","Roose Bolton","Walder Frey"],"correct":"Walder Frey,"},{"id":22,"question":"What is the synonym for killing a king which was Tyrion's main accusation?","options":["Parricide","Regicide","Filicide","Infanticide"],"correct":"Regicide,"},{"id":23,"question":"Which God is also referred to as R'hllor?","options":["The Lord of Light","The Drowned God","The Many Faced God","The Great Stallion"],"correct":"The Lord of Light,"},{"id":24,"question":"What did King Joffrey name his sword?","options":["Lion's Claws","Lightbringer","Heartsbane","Widow's Wail"],"correct":"Widow's Wail,"},{"id":25,"question":"Who was the first character in the show to kill a White Walker?","options":["Jeor Mormont","Samwell Tarly","Alliser Thorne","Jon Snow"],"correct":"Samwell Tarly,"},{"id":26,"question":"What does \"Dracarys\" translates to?","options":["Kill","Dragon Fire","Burn","Attack"],"correct":"Dragon Fire,"},{"id":27,"question":"Who was named King of the Iron Islands during the kingsmoot following Balon's murder?","options":["Yara Greyjoy","Asha Greyjoy","Theon Greyjoy","Euron Greyjoy"],"correct":"Euron Greyjoy,"},{"id":28,"question":"What was the mad king's real name?","options":["Baelor Targaryen","Aemon Targaryen","Aegon Targaryen","Aerys Targaryen"],"correct":"Aerys Targaryen,"},{"id":29,"question":"How was Maester Aemon (Targaryen) and the mad king related?","options":["Cousins","Uncle and nephew","Father and son","Brothers"],"correct":"Uncle and nephew,"},{"id":30,"question":"Who said; \"I grew up with soldiers. I learned how to die a long time ago\"?","options":["Jorah Mormont","Grey Worm (Torgo Nudho)","Ned Stark","Alliser Thorne"],"correct":"Ned Stark,"},{"id":31,"question":"How is Old Nan and Hodor related?","options":["Grandmother and grandson","Mother and son","Aunt and nephew","They are not related"],"correct":"Grandmother and grandson,"},{"id":32,"question":"What is the capital of The Principality of Dorne?","options":["Godsgrace","Starfall","Sandstone","Sunspear"],"correct":"Sunspear,"},null,{"id":34,"question":"Who is nicknamed the \"Sword of the Morning\"?","options":["Ser Arthur Dayne","Ser Duncan the Tall","Ser Barristan Selmy","Lord Howland Reed"],"correct":"Ser Arthur Dayne,"},{"id":35,"question":"Which city of Slavers' Bay (Dragons' Bay) Did Daenerys Stormborn visit first?","options":["Astapor","Meereen","Yunkai","Volantis"],"correct":"Astapor,"},{"id":36,"question":"Who said; \"Never forget what you are. The rest of the world will not.\"?","options":["Tyrion Lannister","Ramsay Bolton","Balon Greyjoy","Roose Bolton"],"correct":"Tyrion Lannister,"},{"id":37,"question":"Which of those is not included in the Seven Kingdoms?","options":["The Iron Islands","The Westerlands","The Riverlands","Dorne"],"correct":"Dorne,"},{"id":38,"question":"How are Melisandre and Kinvara related?","options":["They are not related","Sisters","Cousins","Mother and daughter"],"correct":"They are not related,"},{"id":39,"question":"Who was the Lord Commander of the Kings-Guard at the beginning of the show?","options":["Ser Barristan Selmy","Ser Mandon Moore","Ser Jaime Lannister","Ser Meryn Trant"],"correct":"Ser Barristan Selmy,"},{"id":40,"question":"Who killed Osha?","options":["Myranda ","Ramsay Bolton","Roose Bolton","Theon Greyjoy"],"correct":"Ramsay Bolton,"},{"id":41,"question":"Which city did The Unsullied find almost abandoned as they proceeded to attack it?","options":["Casterly Rock","Yunkai","Lannisport","The Red Keep"],"correct":"Casterly Rock,"},null,{"id":43,"question":"Who saved Brann Stark and Meera Reed from the Wights?","options":["Benjen Stark","Samwell Tarly","Jon Snow","Locke"],"correct":"Benjen Stark,"},{"id":44,"question":"Before taking the black, Locke was fighting for which lord?","options":["Lord Robett Glover","Lord Smalljon Umber","Lord Harald Karstark","Lord Roose Bolton"],"correct":"Lord Roose Bolton,"},{"id":45,"question":"Who killed Ser Amory Lorch?","options":["Robb Stark","The Biter","Janos Slynt","Jaqen H'ghar"],"correct":"Jaqen H'ghar,"},{"id":46,"question":"What's the Western most castle defending The Wall?","options":["The Shadow Tower","Eastwatch","Castle Black","Nightfort"],"correct":"The Shadow Tower,"},{"id":47,"question":"Who killed Jon Arryn?","options":["Sandor \"The Hound\" Clegane","Lysa Arryn","Grand Maester Pycelle","Cersei Lannister"],"correct":"Lysa Arryn,"},{"id":48,"question":"What was Petyr Baelish's (Littlefinger's) last words?","options":["Please...","I loved you...","Sansa...","I loved your mother..."],"correct":"Sansa...,"},{"id":49,"question":"What signals the beginning of the winter season?","options":["White Ravens","Wights","Snow at King's Landing","Scrolls sent by the maesters"],"correct":"White Ravens,"}]}